Guide to the Gary Ware Collection of Martin Wong Letters MSS.299
Fales Library and Special Collections
Gary Ware Collection of Martin Wong Letters
1966-1979
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ware, Gary
MSS.299
0.5 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box
Scope and Content
This collection consists of letters written by Martin Wong to Gary Ware from 1962 to 1975. The letters range in topic from personal affairs to California counterculture to art production.
Arrangement
The letters are arranged chronlogically. When no specific date within a year is known, the letters are arranged by year.
Provenance
Gary Ware donated these letters to Fales in 2010.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
The Martin Wong Papers
The Martin Wong Papers
Correspondence.; Artists and community -- United States; Wong, Martin
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, August, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, July, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, January, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, April, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, May, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- From Martin Wong to Gary Ware, January, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 38)